Guide to the Saybrook College, Yale University, Scrapbooks Maintained by the Master
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Saybrook College, Yale University, scrapbooks maintained by the master
1933-1989
RU 327
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
10.25
The records consist of scrapbooks maintained by the master of Saybrook College, Yale University.
Saybrook College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-K-4 (YRG 13-K-4), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting Saybrook College.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of scrapbooks maintained by the master of Saybrook College, Yale University.
Biographical / Historical
The title "Master" for chief executive officers of residential colleges was changed to "Head of College" in April of 2016.
Student housing; Scrapbooks; Saybrook College (Yale University); Yale University -- Student housing
- Saybrook College scrapbooks, 1933-1989; Accession 1993-A-016
  - 1933-1942 (Box 1)
  - 1942-1951 (Box 2)
  - 1953-1962 (Box 3)
  - 1962-1963, 1943-1946 (Naval) and unidentified (Box 4)
  - Unidentified and loose (Box 5)
  - Unidentified and loose (Box 6)
  - Unidentified and loose (Box 7)
  - Unidentified and loose (Box 8)
  - 1981 (Box 9)